ILGWU Education Department, Kitty Krupat Papers 5780/138
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Consortium for Worker Education: Consortium Board Meetings, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Consortium for Worker Education: Invoices and Payments 1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Consortium for Worker Education: By-laws of Consortium for Worker Education (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Consortium for Worker Education: 1993 Contract Negotiations (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Consortium for Worker Education: Grant Federal Mediation Service 1993-94, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Consortium for Worker Education: Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Consortium for Worker Education: Board of Directors Meeting, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  September 27, 1994
- Cornell University (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Cornell University: Union Leadership Series, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Cornell Spanish Classes Survey, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  September 12, 1994
- Conferences: Freires - Conference, New York, December 5-8, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Conferences: Freire's (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Conferences: Conference on Homework, November 1992, Toronto, Canada (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Conferences: Friere's Conference, "Challenging Education," Dec. 5-7, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  December 5-7, 1991
- Conventions: ILGWU National Convention, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Conventions: Resolutions (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Conventions: Workshops 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Conventions: Convention 92 Videos, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Conventions: 1992 Convention Education Report (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Conventions: Convention 1992 registration materials (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Conventions: Materials of 1989 Convention (Box 15, Folder 5)
- National Conference on Women Garment Workers 3/11/94, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  March 3, 1994
- Workforce Development Focus Groups, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Workforce Development Commission (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Workforce Development Commission (continued) (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Economic Globalization, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Film-Videos Catalogs: Video Request 1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Film-Videos Catalogs: Negotiations, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Film-Videos Catalogs: Construction Audio Project (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Film-Videos Catalogs: Labor X Benefit, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Film-Videos Catalogs: Labor X (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Film-Videos Catalogs, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- We Do The Work (Box 16, Folder 3)
- We Do The Work: Video Newspaper Clippings, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Deep Dish TV Network, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Paper Tiger - Television, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Health Care Materials, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Solidarity Day Video Project 91 Proposal, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Leslie Fay Video Project 9/94, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Leslie Fay Video Project 9/94 (continued), 1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- City LORE, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Labor Law Reform: Labor Law Review (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Labor Law Reform: IUD Working Paper on Labor Law Reform, August 1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Statements, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Reports and Resolutions, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, Chicago, July-Aug. 1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Education Department, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO/UCLEA 1993 Education Conference (Box 17, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO National Education Directors Meeting 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Documents on Reproductive Rites, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Legal Services Program Directory of Attorneys (Box 17, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO "The Florida Project" (Box 17, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Civil Rights Book (Box 17, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO Department of Research, Recession 1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO News, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Bulletins, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Bulletins (continued), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Personnel Matters: Cathy Scott, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Personnel Matters: Erik Lewis Productions, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Personnel Matters: Resumes, 1990-1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Personnel Matters: Payroll Orange Advice Forms, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Personnel Matters: Union Privilege Programs (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Personnel Matters: 1994 sign-up roster for revised retirement booklet (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Personnel Matters: Contract for ILGWU Clerical Local 153, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Personnel Matters: Overtime (Box 18, Folder 11)
- International Federation of Workers Education Association: Report of the 15th General Conference of IFWEA - Lisbon, Portugal, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Labor History: ILG History (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Labor History (Box 19, Folder 1)
- NY 92 NY is fashion history of the ILGWU, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Calendars being held for Kitty Krupat (Box 19, Folder 3)
- El Salvador Newspaper Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- News Articles on Labor Issues, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Articles (News), 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Newspaper Clippings 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- SABA (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Seminars: New England Seminar, Aug. 31-Sept. 2, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Seminars: Northeast Seminar, August 24-26, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Seminars: NJ Staff Seminar, Dec. 1991, Organizing vs. Servicing (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Seminars: Mademoiselle Training Seminar, October 1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Seminars: Leslie Fay Strike Leadership Training, May 6-7, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Solidarity Actions: Rainfair Strike, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Solidarity Actions: El Paso Strike, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Solidarity Actions: Daily News, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Solidarity Actions: May 3, March in solidarity w/ striking workers at Eastern-Greyhound and Domsey, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Solidarity Actions: Pro-choice march, Washington DC, 11/12/89, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  November 12, 1989
- Solidarity Actions: Domsey strikers, activities, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Solidarity Actions: Striker Replacement, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Solidarity Actions: Strikes - various, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Solidarity Actions: naming form, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- National History Day - 1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- National History Day - 1994 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Informative Materials from other countries: South Africa, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Informative Materials from other countries: Sweden, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Justice, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Sexual Harassment (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Labor Management Training Programs, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  March 29, 1993
- Job Referral Counselor: JOBNET forms, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Job Referral Counselor: JOBNET training, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Job Referral Counselor: JOBNET training invitation letters, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Job Referral Counselor: Job referral councilor orientation, October 24-27, 1991, Pocono Manor (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Free Trade: ITGLWF Feature Article, 1990-1992 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Free Trade: News articles on Free Trade, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Free Trade: North American Free Trade Act (NAFTA), 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Free Trade: NAFTA materials, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Meetings-various: Educators Conference, Pittsburgh University, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Meetings - various: Meeting on joint staff training, Saint Louis, June 18-20, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Unity House: New York State District, Sept. 11, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Sept. 11, 1989
- Unity House: Northeast Staff Conference, Unity House, Sept. 13-15, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Labor Education Institute for African-American and Minority Workers (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Duty of Fair Representation (Box 21, Folder 8)
- The Company Store - A Simulation of coal town culture (Box 21, Folder 9)
- How to negotiate (Box 21, Folder 10)
- How People Learn (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Material on Haiti (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Bakery Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Chicago Literacy Project, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  October 8, 1990
- Council on American Fashion, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- New Members Orientation (Box 21, Folder 17)
- China, 1980-1989 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- El Salvador, 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Guatemala (Box 22, Folder 3)
- 1994 Finalists: Victoria Fung (Box 22, Folder 4)
- 1994 Finalists: Lum, Celeste (Box 22, Folder 5)
- 1994 Finalists: Chan, Jimmy (Box 22, Folder 6)
- 1994 Finalists: Kin Chan (Box 22, Folder 7)
- 1994 Finalists: Bloomfield, Mathew L. (Box 22, Folder 8)
- 1994 Finalists: Quang V. Nguyen (Box 22, Folder 9)
- 1994 Finalists: Truong, Mai H. (Box 22, Folder 10)
- 1994 Finalists: Ng, John (Box 22, Folder 11)
- 1994 Finalists: Liu, Jia L. (Box 22, Folder 12)
- 1994 Finalists: Sandy Chan (Box 22, Folder 13)
- 1994 Finalists: Ng, Jennifer (Box 22, Folder 14)
- 1994 Finalists: Julie Wong (Box 22, Folder 15)
- 1994 Finalists: Kin Wong (Box 22, Folder 16)
- 1994 Finalists: Tang, Patrick (Box 22, Folder 17)
- 1994 Finalists: Xu M. Lei (Box 22, Folder 18)
- 1994 Finalists: Gong Mafan P. (Box 22, Folder 19)
- 1994 Finalists: Chin, Cheng W. (Box 22, Folder 20)
- 1994 Finalists: Lo, Andy W. (Box 22, Folder 21)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Dharmesh, Tailor (Box 22, Folder 22)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Ortega-Serrano, Aimee (Box 22, Folder 23)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Yeung, Jason (Box 22, Folder 24)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Selvaggi, Anthony J. (Box 22, Folder 25)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Ng, Norland (Box 23, Folder 1)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Ng, Julio (Box 23, Folder 2)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Ng, Joann (Box 23, Folder 3)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Mui, Peter (Box 23, Folder 4)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Lui, Jane Cy (Box 23, Folder 5)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Kwan, Angela (Box 23, Folder 6)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Lee, Lillian (Box 23, Folder 7)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: He, Jian K (Box 23, Folder 8)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Deebel, Paul W. (Box 23, Folder 9)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Chu, Yung (Box 23, Folder 10)
- 1993 National Scholarship Finalists: Chin, Lynda (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Finalists 1992: Bruzzese, Pamela (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Finalists 1992: Chan, John (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Finalists 1992: Chan, Harry (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Finalists 1992: Chee, Jackson (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Finalists 1992: Chen, Chin Tan (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Finalists 1992: Chechelnitsky, Konstantin (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Finalists 1992: Chew, Andrew (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Finalists 1992: Chen, Qi Xin (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Finalists 1992: Chiu, Faye (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Finalists 1992: Eng, Yuiman (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Finalists 1992: Han, Kam (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Finalists 1992: Kwong, Emma (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Finalists 1992: Lam, Carolyn (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Finalists 1992: Lau, Pauline (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Finalists 1992: Law, Betty M. (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Finalists 1992: Lipari, Joseph (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Finalists 1992: Szczecinski, Lisa A. (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Finalists 1992: Szeto, Yee Wun (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Finalists 1992: Wong, Liza (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Finalists 1992: Chung, Karen (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Finalists 1992: Wong, Allen (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Finalists 1992: Reports (Box 24, Folder 3)
- 1991 Finalists: Andujar, Maritza (Box 24, Folder 4)
- 1991 Finalists: Cao, Dongxi (Box 24, Folder 5)
- 1991 Finalists: Chang, Wahgo Mr. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- 1991 Finalists: Cheng, Kit Ling (Box 24, Folder 7)
- 1991 Finalists: Cheung, Jim W. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- 1991 Finalists: Chiu, Kwok Cheung (Box 24, Folder 9)
- 1991 Finalists: Cho, Johnny (Box 24, Folder 10)
- 1991 Finalists: Chow, Dick Mr. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- 1991 Finalists: Chu, Karen Miss (Box 24, Folder 12)
- 1991 Finalists: Chung, Lang Chun (Box 24, Folder 13)
- 1991 Finalists: Dong, Sherry (Box 24, Folder 14)
- 1991 Finalists: Eng, William (Box 24, Folder 15)
- 1991 Finalists: Feng, Linda (Box 24, Folder 16)
- 1991 Finalists: Law, Josephine Miss (Box 24, Folder 17)
- 1991 Finalists: Lee, Helen (Box 24, Folder 18)
- 1991 Finalists: Lee, Nathan J. Mr. (Box 24, Folder 19)
- 1991 Finalists: Li, Ye Marshal Mr. (Box 24, Folder 20)
- 1991 Finalists: Luca, Luisa (Box 24, Folder 21)
- 1991 Finalists: Nam, Michael Kar-lo (Box 24, Folder 22)
- 1991 Finalists: Ng, Vivian Miss (Box 24, Folder 23)
- 1991 Finalists: Nieta, Glenda Ms. (Box 24, Folder 24)
- 1991 Finalists: Pon, Sau Fee (Box 24, Folder 25)
- 1991 Finalists: Shanks, James A. (Box 24, Folder 26)
- 1991 Finalists: Sanroman, Danny (Box 24, Folder 27)
- 1991 Finalists: Sciangula, Salvatore (Box 24, Folder 28)
- 1991 Finalists: Tan, Tai Ching Miss (Box 24, Folder 29)
- 1991 Finalists: Tsang, Annie Miss (Box 24, Folder 30)
- 1991 Finalists: Wong, David (Box 25, Folder 1)
- 1991 Finalists: Wong, Elaine (Box 25, Folder 2)
- 1991 Finalists: Woo, Becky (Box 25, Folder 3)
- 1991 Finalists: Wu, Bruno Pen (Box 25, Folder 4)
- NON Finalist: Dharmista Patel, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- NON Finalist: Patricia Shigueta, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- NON Finalists: Hiu, Fung Lo 1993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- NON Finalists: Amanda Joseph, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- NON Finalists: Fei Lu Qian, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- NON Finalists: Yeung Chung, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- NON Finalists: Sharpe, Monica Marie 1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- NON Finalists: Salvatore Dimeqlio, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- NON Finalists: Collado, Irette 1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- NON Finalists: Clay, Latoya R. 1993 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- NON Finalists: Edgar, Shannon, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- NON Finalists: Stilson, Thomas K. 1993 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- NON Finalists: Patel, Urvashi 1993 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- NON Finalists: Fritz, Marcia M. 1993 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- NON Finalists: Hake, Stacy L. 1993 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- NON Finalists: Leong, Laura 1994 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- NON Finalists: Brown, Jennifer L. 1993 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- NON Finalists: Corey Watkins, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- NON Finalists: Susanna R. Giardino, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- NON Finalists: Kan Yu (Patricia) Kwan, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- NON Finalists: Baez, Michelle 1993 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- NON Finalists: Zhang Xiang, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- NON Finalists: Espinal, Jose R. 1993 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- NON Finalists: Tomeka L. Henry, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- NON Finalists: Enza M. Navarra, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- A: Acosta, Wanda, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- A: Alvarez, Sandra G., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- A: Andrews, Jennifer, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- A: Anders, Crystal D., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- A: Argandona, Mike E., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- A: Artusa, Antonio, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- B: Borda, Nestor, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- B: Borda, Sandra, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- B: Brewer, Erwin E., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- B: Brown, Beatrice L., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- B: Bauersachs, Valerie D., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- C: Capps, Amelia (Amy) J., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- C: Castillo, Ruddy, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- C: Chiu Meilan, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- C: Chan, Danny, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- C: Chan, Danny K., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- C: Chan, David W., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- C: Chan, Edwin, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- C: Chan, Michael, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- C: Chan, Michele A., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 49)
- C: Chang, Amy, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- C: Chang, George, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- C: Chau, Mee Lee, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- C: Cheung, Bill, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- C: Chin, Chen C., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- C: Chiu, Pul Lee, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- C: Chu, Wendy (Wangee), 1993 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- C: Ciocia, Grace, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- C: Cosimano, Michael V., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- C: Cueva, Ninfa Marie, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- C: Cunningham, Holly D., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- D: De Barros, John, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- D: Derk, Charles R., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- D: DePaolo, Meghan P., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- D: DeVirgilio, Damian, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- D: Dong, Catherine J., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- D: Due, Susan, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- E: Eckhart, Terri, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- E: Elfner, Beth A., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- F: Felder, Andrea B., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- F: Fico, Giulia, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- F: Fields, Martina L., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- G: Garcia, America R., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- G: Gianforte, Joseph, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- G: Gomez, Richard, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- G: Gutienez, Martha J., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Non-finalists Applicants 1994 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- H: Haftl, Gale L., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- H: Herrera, Lilia, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- H: Ho, Chi Chiu, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- H: Ho, Kwok Kin, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- H: Ho, Pei Quan, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- H: Huang, Hui Ru, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- H: Huang, Yuan Qing, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- H: Hugh, Winnie, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- H: Huo, Zhi-Wei, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- I: Iadevaia, Giro, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- I: Intriago, Roger S., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- J: Jones, Jonique K., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- K: Kam, Elain, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- K: Knappenberger, Misty M., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- K: Koo, William Y., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- K: Konschnik, Heather A., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- K: Krow, Shonda C., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- L: Lai, Judy, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- L: Lai, Yuan Hui, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- L: Lau, Margaret, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- L: Lee, Alice Mei, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- L: Lee, Barbara, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- L: Lee, Suet Yee, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- L: Lee, Wai Yin, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- L: Lei, De Wei, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- L: Lei, Zhi Quang, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- L: Leong, Sokin, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- L: Lessane, Ketria N., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- L: Leung, Connie (Ching Han), 1993 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- L: Leung, Kaity, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- L: Leung, Patrick, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- L: Li LiYi, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- L: Liang, Xiao-Dan, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- L: Liang, Yanming, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- L: Liang, So Lan, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- L: Liang, Fei Yan, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- L: Li, Yi Ling, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- L: Lieu, Hoan Tuyet, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- L: Lin, Hao Hong, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- L: Liu, Lisa Ren Yan, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- L: Liu, Nancy Xiao Tao, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- L: Lopez, Henry, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- L: Lora, Rosanna, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- L: Lotito, Dawn M., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- L: Lotiti, Christina A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- M: Mui, Janet, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- M: Morin, Nancy C., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- M: Michelem, Marilyn V., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- M: Mora, Norma, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- M: Mendes, Joseph, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- M: Marinaro, Josephine E., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- M: Mui, Chi Nga (Florence), 1993 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- M: Moy, Meeling, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- M: Meyers, Cynthia L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- M: McAdoo, Jarrod W., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- M: Mattu, Maria, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- M: Martinez, Jamey, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- M: Martin, Stacey, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- M: Marks, Kathy J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- N: New Man, Mercedes A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- N: Ng, Oywah Oy, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- O: Obispo, Lucy, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- P: Pacheco, Juan, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- P: Parillo, Michael, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- P: Patel, Jagruti R., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- P: Pena, Mario E., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- P: Perez, Olga, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- P: Pettit, Marie A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- P: Pica, Angela, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- P: Placenti, Liliana E., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- P: Planinsek, Michael L., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- P: Prentiss, Lisa A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- R: Ramos, Elizabeth, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- R: Reyes, Wilman A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- R: Rodriguez, Norma, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- R: Romero, Ivette G., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- R: Ross, Stephanie R., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- R: Rothstein, Tara, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- S: Sanders, Heidi A., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- S: Seixas, William E., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- S: Shaffer, Matthew J., 1993 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- S: Shick, Susan, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- S: Shum, Sai Cheong, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- S: Sittler, Amy S., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- S: Silvero, Jose O., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- S: Smith, Sheranda, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- S: Solowej, Timothy H., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- S: Sprague, Alicia R., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- S: Suarez, Enrique Fabricio, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- T: Tan, Miaoting, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- T: Tam, Christine, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- T: Toarmina, Salvatore, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- T: Torres, Jose, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- T: Tsang, Alexander, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- T: Tsang, Ellen, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- T: Tsin, Wai Kit, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- T: Tom, Karen, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- V: Valenti, Daniela A., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- V: (Jr.) Vazquez, Jose Luis, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- V: Velazquez, Edward, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- W: Wu, Jie Oi, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- W: Wu, Rong Jie, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- W: Watkins, Corey L., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- W: Wentzel, David K., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- W: Wong, Amy H., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- W: Wong, Chi-Wai, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- W: Wong, Chum-Hung, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- W: Wong, Janet F., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- W: Wong, Lisa, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- W: Wong, Suet Ping, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- W: Wong, Susan, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- W: Wu, Dan Dong, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- W: Wu, Dan Min, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- W: Wu, Hai Fan, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- W: Wu, Yun, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- XYZ: Xaymontry, Didouphanh M., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- XYZ: Zong, Bu E., 1993 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- XYZ: Zhao, Chong Jian, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- XYZ: Zeng, Keyu, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- XYZ: Zeng, Jun Wei (Jennifer), 1993 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- XYZ: Yu, YuQiang, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- XYZ: Yu, Nancy, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- XYZ: Young, Karen, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 41)